California ephemera collection, 1860-
California Ephemera Collection,
- California - Politics and government - 1983 (Box 119)
- California - Politics and government - 1984 (Box 119)
- California - Politics and government - 1985 (Box 119)
- California - Politics and government - 1986 (Box 119)
- California - Politics and government - 1987 (Box 119)
- California - Politics and government - 1990 - (Box 208)
- California - Politics and government - 1998 - 1999 (Box 236)
- California - Politics and government - 2000 - 2001 (Boxes 236, 279)
- California - Politics and government - 2003 - 2010 (Box 279)
- California (newspaper) (Box 16)
  Photostat of 1st page, 1st issue & centennial script.
- California African-American Museum (Box 219)
- California Alligator Farm. Los Angeles, California (Box 11)
- California Anti-Saloon League (Box 11)
- California Army - National Guard (Box 265)
- California Artichoke Advisory Board. Castroville, California (Box 208)
  X. Artichokes.
- California Centennials (Box 148)
  See shelf list for holdings
- California Citrograph (Box 190)
- California Club. Los Angeles, California (Box 148)
- California Clubwoman. Fresno, California (Box 13)
- California Courier. Independent Armenian-American weekly. Fowler, California (Boxes 253, 255)
  Vol. 1, no. 42 (heritage issue), 1958?
  - California courier (Fresno, Calif.)., June 4, 1959.; Item No. 1 (Box 255, Folder 3)
- California Folkore Society (Box 148)
- California Fresh Carrot Advisory Board. Salinas, California (Box 208)
  X Carrots.
- California Fruit Growers Exchange (Box 148)
- California Highway Patrol (Box 236)
- California Historical Society (Box 149)
- California Institute of Technology. Pasadena, California (Box 149)
- California Institute of the Arts (Box 149)
- California Library Association (Box 15)
- California Library Association. Southern Branch. (Box 15)
- California Marine Parks and Harbors Association (Box 16)
- California Museum of Photography (Box 16)
- California Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 16)
- California Pacific International Exposition (1935-1936: San Diego, California) (Box 252)
  Ground Plan California Pacific International Exposition 1935.
  Box 252 is an oversize flat box, 21" x 25"
- California Press Association (Box 16)
- California Redwood Association. San Francisco. (Box 16)
- California Register (Box 16)
- California Roadside Council (Box 191)
- California Safely Surrendered Baby Law (Box 279)
- California State Lottery (Box 16)
- California State Parks (Boxes 236, 279)
- California State Railroad Museum. Sacramento, California (Box 235)
- California State University, Northridge. (Box 219)
- California Teachers Association (Box 16)
- California Western Railroad. Fort Bragg, California (Box 236)
- California, Southern - Description and travel (Boxes 16, 279)
- California, Southern - History (Box 16)
- California, Southern - Religion (Box 16)
- California. Constitution of 1849. (Box 13)
- California. Constitution of 1877. (Box 13)
  xCalifornia - History - Constitution of 1877.
- California. Department of Motor Vehicles. (Box 219)
- California. Legislature. (Box 15)
- California. State Council of Defense. War History Committee. (Box 16)
- California. State Department of Employment. (Box 16)
- California. State Department of Social Welfare. (Box 16)
- California. State Normal School. (Box 190)
- Californians for Liberal Representation (Box 188)
- Californians for Preservation Action (Box 16)
- Californians Inc. (Box 16)
- Caltrans (Box 235)
- Camac, Charles Nicoll Bancker, 1868 - 1940 (Box 16)
- Cambria, California (Box 16)
- Camp Cady, California (Box 16)
- Camp Meeker, California (Sonoma County) (Box 149)
- Campbell, California (Box 265)
- Campbell, William Wallace, 1862 - 1938 (Box 16)
- Camps - California - Southern (Boxes 219, 251)
- Camptonville, California (Box 16)
- Cancer - California (Box 235)
- Canoga Park, California (Box 219)
- Cantwell, John Joseph, Abp., 1874 - 1947 (Box 16)
- Capay Valley, California (Yolo County) (Box 149)
- Car Rental Agencies (Box 235)
- Carlsbad, California (Boxes 195, 235)
- Carmel, California (Boxes 149, 235)
- Carnation Company (Box 16)
- Carpinteria, California (Box 16)
- Carrillo, Juan (Box 149)
- Carrizo Gorge, California (Box 149)
- Carrots.
  SEE: California Fresh Carrots Advisory Board. Salinas, Calif.
- Casinos (Box 279)
- Casmalia, California (Box 265)
- Cat shows - California (Box 208)
- Catholic Church. Archdiocese of Los Angeles. (Box 149)
- Cattle - California, southern (Box 235)
- Caveat (Bookstore) (Box 196)
  Added entry: Cowan, Robert Grannis
- Caves - California (Box 265)
- Cedar Springs, California (Box 265)
- Cemeteries - California (Box 208)
- Censorship - California (Box 150)
- Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions. Santa Barbara, California (Box 150)
- Central Valley Project (California) (Boxes 17, 225)
- Cerritos, California (Box 279)
- Chain restaurants (Box 235)
- Chamber Music - California - Los Angeles (Box 235)
- Chambers, Joseph Fleischman, 1862 - (Box 17)
- Chandler, Harry, 1864 - 1944 (Box 17)
- Chandler, Raymond, 1888 - 1959 (Boxes 18, 199)
- Channel Islands, California (Box 235)
- Charities - California (Boxes 12, 279)
- Charles W. Bowers Memorial Museum. Santa Ana, California (Box 18)
  See shelf list card for subject entries.
- Chase, Joseph Smeaton, 1864 - 1923 (Box 18)
- Chatsworth Park, California (Boxes 18, 150)
- Chess (Box 235)
- Chessman, Caryl Whittier, 1921 - 1961 (Box 18)
- Chevedden, Paul Edward, 1948 - (Box 18)
- Cheviot Hills Baseball Association. Los Angeles, California (Box 235)
- Chico, California (Box 18)
- Child Actors (Box 279)
- Child Care - California (Box 235)
- Children's parties - California (Box 219)
- Childs, Orzo W. (Box 190)
- Chimney Sweeps (Box 208)
- Chinese in California (Boxes 18, 190)
  - The ancient discoverer and the greatest modern exponent of the use of the wonderful life giving Chinese herbs: Dr. Young Chinese Herb Company., ca. 1910.; Item No. 1 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    "Estab. in the U.S. in 1882. 1844 Sutter St., bet. Buchanon and Webster, San Francisco, Cal."
- Chino, California (Box 235)
- Cho, Margaret (Box 265)
- Christie's. Los Angeles (Firm). (Box 219)
- Chula Vista, California (Box 188)
- Churches - California (Box 208)
- Churches - California, Southern (Box 19)
  Subject entry: Mormons in California.
- Citizen News. Hollywood, California (Box 255)
  Last issue,8/28/70, and 1st resumed issue.
- Citizens Committee to Preserve American Freedoms (Box 150)
- Citrus Fruit Industry - California (Box 191)
- City of Industry, California (Box 208)
- City Seals - California (Box 150)
- City Traffic - Los Angeles (Box 150)
- Civil Defense - California (Box 150)
- Civil Rights - California - Los Angeles (Box 194)
  - Negro representation now!., 1956.; Item No. 1 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    "This brochure is based on a pamphlet written by Elaine Ross, and published by the American Labor Party. Use of the material is with permission of ALP"--Back cover.
- Clappe, Louise Amelia Knapp (Smith), 1819 - 1906 (Box 150)
- Claremont, California (Box 150)
- Clark, Branston (Box 150)
- Clark, Champ (James Beauchamp), 1850 - 1921 (Box 150)
- Clark, George A. (Box 20)
- Clark, James Gowdy, 1830 - 1897 (Box 20)
- Clark, Lucy Belen (Sherman), 1851 - 1942 (Box 20)
- Claypole, Edward Waller, 1835 - 1901 (Box 20)
- Clear Lake, California (Box 20)
- Clearlake, California (Box 279)
- Cleland, Robert Glass, 1885 - 1957 (Box 20)
- Clifton's Cafeterias. Los Angeles, California (Box 20)
- Clinch, Bryan James, 1842 - 1906 (Box 20)
- Clinton, Bill, 1946 - (Box 188)
- Clinton, Clifford E., 1900 - 1969 (Box 20)
- Clubs - California (Boxes 13, 279)
  Box 13 - 3 folders.
- Clum, Woodworth, d. 1946 (Box 20)
- Coachella Valley, California (Box 20)
- Coalinga, California (Box 20)
- Cochran, George Ira, 1863 - (Box 20)
- Cole, Cornelius, 1822 - 1924 (Box 20)
- Coleman, William Tell, 1824 - 1893 (Box 20)
- Collectors and collecting (Box 20)
  Antiques
- Collier, Frank C., 1878 - 1948 (Box 20)
- Collier, John Armistead, 1874 - 1947 (Box 20)
- Coloma, California (Box 20)
- Colorado River (Box 151)
- Colorado River Aqueduct (Box 151)
- Colorado River Association. Los Angeles. (Box 151)
- Colton, California (Box 20)
- Colton, David D. (Box 20)
- Columbia, California (Box 20)
- Colusa, California (Box 237)
- Comfort, Will Levington, 1878 - 1932 (Box 20)
- Comic books, strips, etc. (Box 237)
- Commerce, California (Box 219)
- Community Mental Health Services - California (Box 20)
- Community Redevelopment Agency of the City of Los Angeles (Box 188)
- Compton, California (Box 214)
- Computer Dating (Box 20)
- Conaty, Thomas James, 1847 - 1915 (Box 20)
- Concerts - California (Box 20)
- Concerts - Programs (Box 20)
- Conejo Valley, California (Box 188)
- Conference of Historical Societies (Box 21)
- Conferences - California (Box 20)
- Congress of Industrial Organizations. (U.S.) (Box 21)
- Congress of Industrial Organizations. Political Action Committee. (Box 21)
- Connell, Will, 1898 - 1961 (Boxes 151, 199)
- Conservation of Natural Resources - California (Boxes 151, 279)
- Consumer organizations - California (Box 151)
- Consumer prices - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 190, 208)
- Contra Costa County, California (Box 151)
- Cookery - California (Box 198)
- Cookery, American - Californian (Box 151)
- Coolbrith, Ina Donna, 1841 - 1928 (Box 151)
- Cooperative societies - California (Box 151)
- Cooperative societies - Santa Monica (Box 151)
- Cord Blood Registry. San Bruno, California (Box 237)
- Corona Del Mar, California (Boxes 208, 265)
- Corona, California (Box 151)
- Coronado Islands. Baja, California (Box 152)
- Coronado, California (Box 152)
- Costa Mesa, California (Box 188)
- Cotati, California (Sonoma County) (Box 152)
- Coulter family (Box 152)
- Coulterville, California (Box 237)
- Council for Planning and Conservation. Los Angeles. (Box 152)
- Council on Foreign Policy. Los Angeles. (Box 22)
- Country Clubs (Box 237)
- Coupons (Retail) (Box 237)
- Court Journal, Los Angeles, California. 60th anniversary issue. (Box 261)
- Covina, California (Box 196)
- Cowan, Robert Ernest, 1862 - 1942 (Box 22)
- Craft and Folk Art Museum. Los Angeles. (Box 22)
- Crank, Mrs. James Fillmore, 1846 - 1932 (Box 22)
- Cranston, Alan MacGregor, 1914 - (Box 22)
  With subject entry: Cranston, Alan MacGregor, 1914 - - Portrait
- Crescent City, California (Box 22)
- Crestline, California (Boxes 226, 279)
- Crestwood Hills. Los Angeles, California (Box 279)
- Crime and criminals - California (Box 22)
- Crime Prevention - California (Box 279)
- Crocker, Templeton, 1884 - 1948 (Box 22)
- Crocker, William Henry, 1861 - 1937 (Box 22)
- Crowder, Guy (Box 191)
- Crowley, John J., 1891 - 1940 (Box 22)
- Cukor, George Dewey, 1899 - (Box 186)
- Culpepper, Carl Wagley (Box 22)
- Cultural Heritage Foundation (Box 22)
- Cultural News. Los Angeles, California (Box 251)
  Japanese language, music and arts.
- Culver City Bus. Culver City, California (Boxes 208, 265)
- Culver City, California (Boxes 208, 265)
  Box 265 - 3 folders.
- Culver City, California - Restaurants (Box 279)
- Cunningham, Imogen, 1883 - 1976 (Box 22)
- Curtis, Edward Sheriff, 1868 - 1952 (Box 22)
- Cycling - California (Box 219)
- Dairying - California, Southern (Box 152)
- Dana Point, California (Boxes 195, 279)
- Dance - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 252, 279)
- Dance - California - Study and teaching (Box 237)
- Dancing (Box 23)
- Dancing - UCLA - 1965 - 1970 (Box 23)
- Dancing - UCLA - 1970 - (Box 23)
- Darrow, Clarence Seward, 1857 - 1938 (Box 152)
- Daughters of the American Revolution. California State Society. (Box 186)
- Davis, Edward Michael, 1916 - (Box 24)
  Subject entry for - Portrait.
- Davis, Gray (Box 237)
- Davis, James Edgar, 1889? - 1949 (Box 24)
- Dawson, Ernest, 1882 - 1947 (Box 194)
- Dawson, Glen, 1912 - (Box 188)
- De Longpre, Paul, 1855 - 1911 (Box 25)
- Death Valley (California and Nevada) (Box 237)
- Death Valley '49ers, Inc. (Boxes 120, 214)
  Box 120 - 3 folders. Box 214 is an oversize box.
- Death Valley National Monument (Box 24)
- Death Valley National Park (Box 225)
- Death Valley, California (Boxes 251, 279)
- Debs, Ernest E. (Box 24)
- Deignan, Osborn Warren (Box 24)
- Del Mar, California (Boxes 237, 279)
- Del Monte, California (Box 24)
- Delano, California (Box 196)
- Delmas, Delphin Michael, 1844 - 1928 (Box 24)
- Democratic National Party. Los Angeles. (Box 254)
- Democratic Party. California. (Box 25)
- Democratic Party. California. 1964 - 1965. (Box 25)
- Democratic Party. California. 1966 - 1967 (Box 25)
- Democratic Party. California. Los Angeles. To 1965. (Box 25)
- Democratic Party. California. State Central Committee. (Box 25)
- Democratic Party. California. To 1964. (Box 25)
- Democratic Party. National Convention. Los Angeles. 1960. (Box 121)
- Demonstration for Palestine Committee. Los Angeles. (Box 25)
- Dentistry (Box 237)
- Department stores - California - Los Angeles (Box 188)
- Derby, George Horatio, 1823 - 1861 (Box 25)
- Descanso Gardens. La Canada, California (Box 279)
- Desert Hot Springs, California (Boxes 25, 279)
- Desert Magazine. El Centro, California (Box 265)
- Desert Protective Council, Inc. (Box 25)
- Desert Trail. Twentynine Palms, California (Box 190)
- Deserts (Box 25)
- Diana, Princess of Wales (Box 225)
- Diapers (Box 265)
- Diehl, Digby Robert, 1940 - (Box 153)
- Diet - California (Box 153)
- Disabled - Employment - California (Box 194)
- Disneyland. Anaheim, California (Boxes 153, 237, 252, 264, 279)
  Box 237 - California Adventure. Box 252 is an oversize flat box, 21" x 25". Box 264 - 2 folders.
- Dixon, Maynard, 1875 - 1946 (Box 26)
- Dixon, Thomas, 1864 - 1936 (Box 26)
- Dockweiler, John Henry, 1864? - 1941 (Box 26)
- Dodge, Arthur Burnside, 1863 - 1952 (Box 26)
- Doherty, William, 1940 - 1972 (Box 26)
  See shelf list for subject entries.
- Domestic violence (Box 237)
- Dominguez, Guadelupe (Box 26)
- Donnatin, Charles E. (Box 26)
- Donner Lake, California (Box 26)
- Donner Party (Box 26)
- Douglas County, California (Box 26)
- Douglas, Helen Gahagan, 1900 - (Box 188)
- Dowling, George Thomas, 1847 - 1928 (Box 26)
- Downey, John Gately, 1827 - 1894 (Box 26)
- Downey, Sheridan, 1884 - 1961 (Box 26)
- Drug abuse - California - prevention (Box 219)
- Drugs - California (Box 196)
- Drum Barracks Civl War Museum. Wilmington, California (Box 194)
- Duarte, California (Box 26)
- Ducommun, Charles Louis, 1820 - 1896 (Box 26)
- Dude ranches - California (Box 219)
- Dudley Do-Right Emporium. Hollywood, California (Box 237)
- Dunbar Economic Development Corporation. Los Angeles. (Box 219)
- Duncan's Mills, California (Box 279)
- Dunne, John Gregory (Box 26)
- Dunsmuir, California (Box 26)
- Duran, Narciso, 1776 - 1846 (Box 26)
- Dutch Flat, California (Box 26)
- Dykstra, Clarence Addison, 1883 - 1950 (Box 26)
- Eagle Rock, California (Box 26)
- Eames, Charles and Ray (Boxes 237, 265)
- Earl, Edwin T., 1857? - 1919 (Box 26)
- Earthquake Safety - California (Box 279)
- Earthquakes - California, southern (Box 122)
  5 folders.
- Earthquakes - Los Angeles - 1971 (Box 123)
- Earthquakes - Los Angeles - 1994 (Box 209)
- East Hollywood, California (Box 261)
  Lincoln Tract.
- East Los Angeles College. Los Angeles, California (Boxes 209, 253, 255)
  - La vida nueva., February 26, 1969-.; Item No. 1 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Black guard., April 28, 1969-.; Item No. 2 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    An East Los Angeles College student paper emphasizing civil and social reform issues pertinent to African Americans.
- Ecology - California (Box 154)
- Edelstein, Jerome Melvin, 1924 - (Box 220)
- Education - California (Box 27)
- Edwards Air Force Base, California (Box 265)
- Edwards, Walter Alison, 1862 - (Box 26)
- Ehlers, Alice, 1887 - 1981 (Box 26)
- Eichler (Box 265)
- El Cajon, California (Box 26)
- El Dorado County, California (Box 26)
- El Monte, California (Boxes 26, 220)
- El Pueblo de Los Angeles State Historic Park (Box 26)
  - Viva El Pueblo brochure., ca. 1971.; Item No. 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Promotional brochure for El Pueblo de Los Angeles State Historic Park, located in the Old Plaza near downtown Los Angeles.
- El Pueblo de Los Angeles, Inc. (Box 26)
- El Segundo, California (Box 26)
- El Teatro Campesino. San Juan Bautista, California (Box 275)
- Elections - California - 1964 - 1965 (Box 124)
- Elections - California - 1966 - 1978 (Box 124)
- Elections - California - 1996 (Box 220)
- Elections - California - 2004 (Box 264)
- Elections - California - prior to 1964 (Box 124)
- Elections - Los Angeles (Box 26)
- Elections - Los Angeles - 1930 - 1932 (Box 26)
- Elections - Los Angeles - 1933 - 1935 (Box 26)
- Elections - Los Angeles - 1965 - (Box 28)
- Elections - Ventura County - 1933 - 1935 (Box 28)
- Electroplating (Box 265)
- Elkhorn Slough (California) (Box 237)
- Elks (Fraternal Order) (Box 191)
- Elsinore, Lake (Box 28)
- Elysium Institute. Topanga, California (Box 220)
- Elysium, Inc. (Box 28)
- Emergency preparedness (Boxes 237, 279)
- Emeryville, California (Box 279)
- Emeryville, California - Mudflat. (Box 28)
- Emigres - California (Box 191)
- Encinitas, California (Box 28)
- Encino, California (Box 28)
- Endangered species - California (Box 188)
- Energy conservation - California (Box 28)
  X. Conservation of energy.
- Englebright, William F., 1855 - 1915 (Box 28)
- Entertainment memorabilia (Box 237)
- Environmental Education - California (Box 188)
- Environmental Protection - California (Box 220)
- Escondido, California (Box 28)
- Espey, John Jenkins, 1913 - (Box 28)
- Essex, California (Box 265)
- Estate Project for Artists with AIDS (Box 196)
- Eucalyptus (Box 28)
- Evangelists (Box 188)
- Event planning (Box 237)
- Everson, William, 1912 - (Box 29)
- Exeter, California (Box 29)
- Express Highways - Los Angeles (Box 29)
  X. Freeways. 1. Los Angeles.
- Fair Oaks, California (Sacramento County) (Box 29)
- Fair Trade LA (Box 280)
- Fairfield, California (Box 265)
- Fallbrook, California (Box 29)
- Family Publications (Box 265)
- Farmers' Markets - California (Box 280)
- Farquhar, Francis Peloubet, 1887 - 1974 (Box 29)
- Farwell, Arthur George, 1872 - (Box 29)
- Faulkner Memorial Art Gallery. Santa Barbara, California (Box 29)
  1. Art - Santa Barbara - Galleries and museums
- Federal Writers Project (Box 29)
  1. Art - Galleries and museums
- Federation of Hillside and Canyon Associations (Box 29)
- Felton, California (Boxes 237, 280)
- Fencing - California (Box 191)
- Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1919 - (Box 29)
- Festivals - California (Boxes 153, 265)
- Festivals - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 153, 265)
  - Festivals of Los Angeles., 1996.; Item No. 1 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    Pamphlet features a calendar of festivals in the city of Los Angeles, featuring the diversity of cultural events. Includes festivals organized by African American, Mexican American, Native American, Chinese American, and Japanese American communities, and others.
- Fifth (5th) District Record. Los Angeles, California (Box 251)
  1965 Mar 30.
- Fillmore and Western Railway Co. Fillmore, California (Box 237)
- Fillmore, California (Box 153)
- Film Festivals - California - Los Angeles (Box 280)
- Film festivals - Los Angeles (Box 237)
- Film societies (Boxes 237, 265)
- Filoli. Woodside, California (Box 280)
- Finkle, Frederick Cecil, 1865? - 1948 (Box 29)
- Fire engines (Box 29)
- Fire Safety - California (Box 280)
- Fires (Box 209)
- First Century Families (Box 153)
- Fisher, Mary Frances Kennedy, 1908 - (Box 153)
- Fishes - California (Box 153)
- Fishing industry - California (Boxes 153, 266)
- Flanner, Hildegarde, 1899 - (Box 153)
- Flint, Frank Putnam, 1862 - 1929 (Box 153)
- Flintridge, California (Box 196)
- Flores Magon, Enrique (Box 153)
  - The last call to radicals., ca. 1916.; Item No. 1 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    Flier encouraging solicitation of funds to assist in the Magon brothers' appeal, on the grounds of defending freedom of the press.
  - Open letter, 1916 May 15, Los Angeles Calif., from Edgcumb Pinchon, General Secretary, Workers' International Defense League., May 15, 1916.; Item No. 2 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    Open letter encouraging solicitation of funds to aid in the trail of the Magon brothers.
  - Wanted: a letter!., ca. 1915.; Item No. 3 (Folder 2)
    Handbill encouraging people to write letters to the judge and the district attorney supervising the Magon brothers' trial
  - El Regeneracin clipping., 1916 July 2.; Item No. 4 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - El Regeneracin clipping., 1916 March 4.; Item No. 5 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Justice and not bullets., undated.; Item No. 6 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - The Magons sentenced: help us appeal., July 1916.; Item No. 7 (Box 153, Folder 2)
- Flowers (Box 154)
- Flying saucers (Box 30)
- Folk Tree. Pasadena, California (Box 186)
- Folsom, California (Box 30)
- Fontana, California (Box 30)
- Food - models (Box 196)
- Football (Box 237)
- Foothill Transit (Box 266)
- Foothill Transit. West Covina, California (Box 237)
- Ford, John Anson, 1883 - (Box 30)
- Forest Lawn Memorial Park. Glendale, California (Boxes 30, 261)
- Forests and forestry - California (Box 30)
- Fort Bidwell, California (Box 30)
- Fort Bragg, California (Box 188)
- Fort Independence, California (Box 266)
- Fort Ross, California (Box 30)
- Fort Tejon, California (Kern County) (Box 30)
- Foshay, James A., 1856 - 1914 (Box 30)
- Foster & Kleiser (Box 30)
  Missing 05/06/2003
- Foster, Stephen Clark, 1820 - 1898 (Box 30)
- Fountain Valley, California (Box 266)
- Fowler, California (Box 237)
- Francis Bacon Library (Box 30)
  X. Claremont College, Claremont, Calif. Francis Bacon Library.
- Francis, Jack C. (Box 30)
- Francis, John Haywood, 1867 - (Box 30)
- Frasher, Burton, 1888 - 1955 (Box 30)
  1. Frashers Fotos. 2. Pomona, Calif.
- Fraternities - College (Box 191)
- Fraternity Elysia. Los Angeles County, California (Box 266)
- Fredericks, John D. (Box 30)
- Freemasons. California. Scottish Rite. (Box 30)
- Fremont, John Charles, 1813 - 1891 (Box 31)
- French in California (Box 31)
- Fresh Garlic Association. Sausalito, California (Box 186)
- Fresno County, California (Box 31)
- Fresno Grizzlies (Baseball team) (Box 280)
- Fresno, California (Box 31)
- Friday Morning Club. Los Angeles. (Box 31)
- Friends of the Archival Center (Box 31)
- Friends of the Santa Monica Mountains, Parks and Seashore. Los Angeles. (Box 31)
- Friends of the UCLA Library (Box 31)
- Friends, Society of. American Friends Service Committee. Southern California Branch. (Box 31)
- Fullerton, California (Boxes 31, 199)
- Furniture industry and trade - California, Southern (Box 155)
- G. Ray Hawkins Gallery, Inc. Los Angeles. (Box 155)
  4 folders. Subject entry for - Portrait.
- Gage, Henry T. (Box 32)
- Gamble House. Pasadena, California (Box 280)
- Gambling - California, Southern (Box 32)
- Gambling on Indian reservations - California (Boxes 238, 280)
- Gambling ships - California (Box 32)
- Garberville, California (Box 280)
- Garden Grove, California (Box 188)
- Gardena, California (Box 266)
- Gardening Services (Box 266)
- Gardens (Box 32)
- Garland, Virginia (Box 32)
- Garland, William May, 1866? - 1948 (Box 32)
- Gay Pride - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 266, 280)
  Pride Magazine. West Hollywood, Calif.
- Gay rights - California (Box 238)
- Gays and lesbians - directories - southern California (Box 256)
- Gay's Lion Farm. El Monte, California (Box 32)
- Geisel, Theodor Seuss, 1904 - (Box 32)
- Gemological Institute of America. Santa Monica, California (Box 209)
- Gene Autry Western Heritage Museum. Los Angeles, California (Boxes 196, 238)
- General Hershey Bar (Box 263)
- General Phineas Banning residence (Box 32)
  X. Banning, Phinease, 1830 - 1885.
- Genthe, Arnold, 1869 - 1942 (Box 199)
  Box 199 is an oversize flat box.
- George Pepperdine College. Los Angeles. (Box 32)
  See shelf list for subject entires.
- Georgetown, California (Box 32)